Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. Competitive Advertisements, Pre-55 Group, 1894-1957
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Container List
  - Beverages
    - Wines and Liquors
      - Courvoisier, 1936-1948, (2 folders) (Box 48)
      - Crab Orchard, 1934-1939, (3 folders) (Box 48)
      - de Kuyper, 1941-1954, (5 folders) (Box 48)
      - Dewar's, 1936-1938, (2 folders) (Box 48)
      - Dewar's White Label, 1945-1954, (8 folders) (Box 48)
      - Dixie Belle Gin, 1942-1949, (4 folders) (Box 48)
      - Don Q Rum, 1939-1952, (5 folders) (Box 48)
      - Drambuie, 1941-1954, (2 folders) (Box 48)
      - Eagle, 1937-1941, (2 folders) (Box 48)
      - Early Times, 1941-1942, 1951-1953, (4 folders) (Box 48)
      - Fleischmann's Whiskey, 1934-1937, (3 folders) (Box 48)
      - Fleischmann's Whiskey, 1938-1954, (10 folders) (Box 49)
      - Fleischmann's Gin, 1935-1954, (7 folders) (Box 49)
      - Frankfort, 1933-1941, (2 folders) (Box 49)
      - Four Roses, 1934-1940, (7 folders) (Box 49)
      - Four Roses, 1941-1954, (14 folders) (Box 50)
      - Gallagher & Burton, 1933-1954, (8 folders) (Box 50)
      - Gilbey's Gin and Scotch, 1935 (Box 50)
      - Gilbey's Scotch, 1945-1954, (6 folders) (Box 50)
      - Gilbey's Gin, 1943 (Box 50)
      - Gilbey's Gin, 1945-1954, (6 folders) (Box 51)
      - Glenmore Kentucky Bourbon, 1943-1954, (3 folders) (Box 51)
      - Gordon's Gin, 1943-1954, (7 folders) (Box 51)
      - Government House Rum, 1936-1944, (2 folders) (Box 51)
      - Grant's Scotch, 1936-1938, 1947-1948, (2 folders) (Box 51)
      - Harwood's, 1946-1948, (3 folders) (Box 51)
      - Hennessy, 1942-1954, (4 folders) (Box 51)
      - Heublein's, 1942-1954, (10 folders) (Box 51)
      - Hiram Walker's DeLuxe, 1944-1954, (9 folders) (Box 51)
      - Hiram Walker Dry Martini, 1945-1947, (2 folders) (Box 51)
      - Hiram Walker, 1953 (Box 51)
      - Hiram Walker's Gin, 1945-1946, (2 folders) (Box 51)
      - Hiram Walker's Gin, 1947-1954, (2 folders) (Box 52)
      - Holland House, 1945-1954, (2 folders) (Box 52)
      - Hunter Kentucky Bourbon, 1938-1954, (3 folders) (Box 52)
      - I.W. Harper, 1942-1948, (2 folders) (Box 52)
      - Jamaica Rums, 1942-1948, (2 folders) (Box 52)
      - James E. Pepper, 1945-1953, (4 folders) (Box 52)
      - Johnnie Walker, 1942-1954, (11 folders) (Box 52)
      - Kinsey Gin, 1945-1947, (3 folders) (Box 52)
      - Lejon Brandy, 1942-1950, (4 folders) (Box 52)
      - Martell, 1947-1954, (2 folders) (Box 52)
      - Martin's V.V.O. Scotch, 1943-1954, (4 folders) (Box 52)
      - M & M (Mattingly & Moore), 1942-1943, (2 folders) (Box 52)
      - Melrose, 1942-1950, (3 folders) (Box 52)
      - Merito, 1942-1952, (4 folders) (Box 52)
      - Milshire Gin, 1934-1945, (3 folders) (Box 52)
      - Mount Vernon, 1935-1953, (11 folders) (Box 53)
      - Myers's Rum, 1938-1954, (7 folders) (Box 53)
      - National Distillers, 1933-1949, (6 folders) (Box 53)
      - Old Angus, 1938-1952, (8 folders) (Box 53)
      - Old Bushmills, 1936, 1941-1942, (2 folders) (Box 53)
      - Old Charter Bourbon, 1942-1954, (6 folders) (Box 53)
      - Old Crow, 1935-1950, (11 folders) (Box 53)
      - Old Crow, 1951-1954, (4 folders) (Box 54)
      - Old Drum, 1936-1941, (3 folders) (Box 54)
      - Old Fitzgerald, 1943-1954, (8 folders) (Box 54)
      - Old Forester, 1938-1954, (13 folders) (Box 54)
      - Old Grand-Dad, 1936-1951, (12 folders) (Box 54)
      - Old Grand-Dad, 1952-1954, (3 folders) (Box 55)
      - Old Hickory, 1949-1954, (2 folders) (Box 55)
      - Old Overholt, 1934-1954, (12 folders) (Box 55)
      - Old Smuggler, 1947-1954, (4 folders) (Box 55)
      - Old Sunny Brook, 1945-1954, (4 folders) (Box 55)
      - Old Taylor, 1936-1954, (11 folders) (Box 55)
      - Old Thompson, 1945-1954, (9 folders) (Box 55)
      - Park and Tilford, 1939-1941, (2 folders) (Box 55)
      - Park and Tilford, 1942-1954, (12 folders) (Box 56)
      - Pete Hagen's Cocktails, 1943-1946, (3 folders) (Box 56)
      - Peter Dawson, 1941-1952, (3 folders) (Box 56)
      - Pilgrim Rum, 1944-1947, (3 folders) (Box 56)
      - Puerto Rican Rum, 1949-1950, (2 folders) (Box 56)
      - Rums of Puerto Rico, 1952-1954, (2 folders) (Box 56)
      - Remy Martin, 1946-1951 (Box 56)
      - Riondo Rum, 1941-1952, (4 folders) (Box 56)
      - Ronrico Rum, 1944-1952, (3 folders) (Box 56)
      - Seagram's, 1934-1941, (8 folders) (Box 57)
      - Seagram's Gin, 1945-1954, (7 folders) (Box 57)
      - Siboney Rum, 1936-1947, (3 folders) (Box 57)
      - Smirnoff, 1934-1954, (3 folders) (Box 57)
      - SoCo (Southern Comfort), 1941-1954, (4 folders) (Box 57)
      - Teacher's, 1946-1954, (4 folders) (Box 57)
      - Three Feathers, 1934-1950, (17 folders) (Box 58)
      - Vat 69, 1934-1948, (15 folders) (Box 58)
      - Vat 69, 1949-1954, (6 folders) (Box 59)
      - J. Wile, 1941 (Box 59)
      - White Horse, 1933-1953, (19 folders) (Box 59)
      - Wilson, 1937-1953, (10 folders) (Box 59)
    - Beer and non-alcoholic beer, 1917-1927, (2 folders) (Box 60)
    - Brandy and cognac
      - Miscellaneous, 19363-1954, (11 folders) (Box 60)
      - Arrow, 1941-1943 (Box 60)
      - Christian Brothers, 1941 (Box 60)
      - Croix Royale, 1945 (Box 60)
      - DuBouchet, 1953-1954 (Box 60)
      - Fendador (Pedro Domecq), 1941 (Box 60)
      - Hiblick, 1941 (Box 60)
      - Ron Rey, 1944-1946 (Box 60)
    - Cocktails and mixers
      - Miscellaneous, 1936-1946 (Box 60)
      - Eggnog miscellaneous, 1947 (Box 60)
      - Crosse and Blackwell, 1950 (Box 60)
      - Overbrooks Eggnog, 1942-1954 (Box 60)
    - Cordials and Liqueurs
      - Miscellaneous, 1936-1954, (13 folders) (Box 60)
      - Amer Picon, 1936 (Box 60)
      - Arrow, 1947-1949 (Box 60)
      - Bardinet, 1942 (Box 60)
      - Croix Royale, 1945 (Box 60)
      - Cointreau, 1945-1954 (Box 60)
      - DuBouchet, 1953-1954 (Box 60)
      - Plantation, 1946 (Box 60)
      - Red House, 1944-1945 (Box 60)
      - Swanee Pride/Old Melody, 1944-1946 (Box 60)
      - Southland Nectar/Cocktail Hour, 1945-1946 (Box 60)
    - Gin
      - Miscellaneous, 1936-1947, (6 folders) (Box 60)
      - Miscellaneous, 1948-1950 (Box 61)
      - Barclay's, 1945-1947 (Box 61)
      - Cummins Collins, 1945-1946 (Box 61)
      - Gladstone, 1943-1947 (Box 61)
      - Gold Medal, 1945-1946 (Box 61)
      - Graves, 1945-1947 (Box 61)
      - House of Kasser, 1945-1946 (Box 61)
      - Lloyd's, 1945-1946 (Box 61)
    - Rum
      - Miscellaneous, 1936-1952, (7 folders) (Box 61)
      - Caldwell's, 1944-1946 (Box 61)
      - Carioca, 1942-1947 (Box 61)
      - Daiquiri, 1941 (Box 61)
      - El Padre, 1944-1945 (Box 61)
      - Havana Club, 1944-1945 (Box 61)
      - Jamaica, 1952 (Box 61)
      - Marimba, 1944-1945 (Box 61)
      - Marin, 1944 (Box 61)
      - Old Medford, 1944-1946 (Box 61)
      - Old St. Croix, 1944-1945 (Box 61)
      - Pedro's, 1944-1946 (Box 61)
      - Port Royal, 1943-1945 (Box 61)
      - Rhum Negrita, 1936-1938 (Box 61)
    - Whiskey
      - Miscellaneous, 1934-1954, (14 folders) (Box 61)
      - Liquor stores, 1934 (Box 61)
      - Department stores, 1934 (Box 61)
      - Bond & Lillard, 1945-1946 (Box 62)
      - Bourbon de Luxe, 1954 (Box 62)
      - Calvert, 1936, 1953-1954, (2 folders) (Box 62)
      - Canadian Club, 1954 (Box 62)
      - Century Club, 1943 (Box 62)
      - Charter Oak, 1951 (Box 62)
      - Chivas Regal, 1952-1954 (Box 62)
      - Cobb's Creek, 1936-1937 (Box 62)
      - County Fair, 1950 (Box 62)
      - Cream of Kentucky, 1948-1949 (Box 62)
      - Dominion 10, 1953-1954 (Box 62)
      - Fine Arts, 1941-1945 (Box 62)
      - Gibson's, 1936-1938 (Box 62)
      - G&W 5 Star, 1942-1943 (Box 62)
      - Grand MacNish, 1941 (Box 62)
      - Green River, 1941 (Box 62)
      - Guckenheimer, 1951 (Box 62)
      - Hudson's Bay, 1951-1954 (Box 62)
      - Highland Queen, 1947-1948 (Box 62)
      - Jack Daniel's, 1952-1954 (Box 62)
      - Kentucky Tavern, 1954 (Box 62)
      - Kessler's, 1943 (Box 62)
      - King, 1943-1945 (Box 62)
      - King's Ransom, 1936-1942 (Box 62)
      - King William IV, 1936-1943 (Box 62)
      - Lansdowne Reserve, 1943-1946 (Box 62)
      - MacNaughton's, 1951-1954 (Box 62)
      - Medley Brothers, 1951-1952 (Box 62)
      - Old American, 1936 (Box 62)
      - Old Colony, 1934 (Box 62)
      - Old Dutch, 1934 (Box 62)
      - Old Hermitage, 1945-1947 (Box 62)
      - Old Mr. Boston, 1940-1943 (Box 62)
      - Old Poindexter, 1945-1946 (Box 62)
      - Old Quaker, 1949-1950 (Box 62)
      - PM, 1940-1954 (Box 62)
      - Pebbleford, 1947-1948 (Box 62)
      - Philadelphia, 1941 (Box 62)
      - Roamer, 1945-1946 (Box 62)
      - Schenley, 1954 (Box 62)
      - Town Tavern, 1935 (Box 62)
      - William Penn, 1942-1943 (Box 62)
    - Vodka, 1946-1954 (Box 62)
    - Wine, Bitters, Sherry, etc.
      - Angostura bitters, 1933-1950, (10 folders) (Box 62)
      - Cresta Blanca, 1950-1952, (3 folders) (Box 62)
      - DuBonnet, 1945-1953 (Box 63)
      - G&D, 1941-1942, (2 folders) (Box 63)
      - Gold Seal wines, 1946-1953, (2 folders) (Box 63)
      - Italian Swiss Colony, 1946-1950, (4 folders) (Box 63)
      - Mouquin, 1933 (Box 63)
      - Mumm's, 1934-1935 (Box 63)
      - N.Y. State Widmer's, 1944-1953, (2 folders) (Box 63)
      - Roma wines, 1944-1953, (9 folders) (Box 63)
      - Sandeman, 1938 (Box 63)
      - Valiant, 1944-1950, (6 folders) (Box 63)
      - Wine miscellaneous, 1943-1947, (4 folders) (Box 63)
      - Wine miscellaneous, 1947-1954, (8 folders) (Box 64)
      - Sherry and vermouth, 1943-1954, (4 folders) (Box 64)
      - Vermouth and bitters, 1946-1950 (Box 64)
      - Wine/sherry/champagne, 1934-1941, (2 folders) (Box 64)
      - Fruit industry, 1935-1937 (Box 64)
      - Liqueur miscellaneous, 1942 (Box 64)
      - Liqueur miscellaneous, 1934 (Box 65)
      - McKesson & Robbins, 1935 (Box 65)
      - Moet & Chandon, 1934-1935 (Box 65)
      - Miscellaneous, 1935-1937, (3 folders) (Box 65)
  - Store Advertising
    - Department stores, 1951-1954, (3 folders) (Box 66)
    - Grocery stores, 1950-1953, (2 folders) (Box 66)
    - Electrical appliance stores, 1948 (Box 66)
    - Specialty stores
      - Saks Fifth Avenue, 1943-1953, (10 folders) (Box 66)
      - Best & Co., 1947-1953, (5 folders) (Box 66)
      - Miscellaneous, 1954 (Box 66)
  - Drug Products
    - Cold remedies, 1914-1933 (Box 67)
    - Cough drops, 1919-1948 (Box 67)
    - Cough remedy miscellaneous, 1929-1954 (Box 67)
    - Soap
      - Jap Rose, 1921-1928 (Box 67)
      - Lifebuoy, 1938-1953 (Box 67)
    - Antiseptics
      - Listerine, 1945-1954 (Box 67)
      - Lysol, 1945-1946 (Box 67)
      - Procter & Gamble, 1944 (Box 67)
    - Analgesics
      - Bayer aspirin, 1945-1954 (Box 67)
      - Ben-Gay, 1945-1953 (Box 67)
      - Topical treatments, 1938-1954 (Box 67)
    - Laxatives
      - Phillips Milk of Magnesia, 1930-1934 (Box 67)
      - Sal Hepatica, 1926-1950 (Box 67)
      - Petrolatum, 1930-1934 (Box 67)
      - Squibb corporate, 1930-1942 (Box 67)
      - Laxative/antacid miscellaneous, 1922-1946 (Box 67)
    - Dentrifices and toothpaste
      - Pebeco, 1917-1921 (Box 68)
      - Pepsodent, 1926-1939 (Box 68)
      - Pyorrhocide, 1918-1929 (Box 68)
      - Tooth miscellaneous, 1925-1943 (Box 68)
      - Denture adhesives, 1941-1950 (Box 68)
      - Squibb Dental Cream, 1923-1935, (5 folders) (Box 68)
  - Tobacco--Cigarettes
    - Camel, 1926-1932, (5 folders) (Box 69)
    - Fatima, 1927-1930 (Box 69)
  - Drug Products
    - Dentrifices and toothpaste
      - Ipana (Box 70)
    - Foot Aids
      - Allen's, 1929-1953, (13 folders) (Box 70)
      - B. Nelson, Blue Jay, 1925-1953, (20 folders) (Box 70)
      - Blue Jay, 1922-1924 (Box 71)
      - Callous-Ease, 1932 (Box 71)
      - Cal-O-Cide, 1928-1931 (Box 71)
      - Coolene, 1925-1932, (3 folders) (Box 71)
      - Cro-Pax, 1941 (Box 71)
      - Freezone, 1928-1939, (9 folders) (Box 71)
      - Johnson's Foot Soap, 1941-1943, (12 folders) (Box 71)
      - Ice Mint, 1915-1953, (11 folders) (Box 71)
      - Gets-It, 1922-1931, (4 folders) (Box 71)
      - Johnson & Johnson, 1934-1937 (Box 71)
      - Jung's Arch Brace, 1916-1933, (4 folders) (Box 71)
      - Kohler, 1930-1934, (2 folders) (Box 71)
      - Lock's, 1942 (Box 71)
      - Phytosin, 1930 (Box 71)
      - Scholl, 1945-1953, (9 folders) (Box 71)
      - Squibb, 1922-1924 (Box 71)
    - Pharmaceutical houses
      - Squibb, 1942-1952, (7 folders) (Box 72)
      - Upjohn, 1947-1953, (6 folders) (Box 72)
      - Wyeth, 1945-1953, (9 folders) (Box 72)
      - Miscellaneous, 1943-1954, (7 folders) (Box 72)
      - Institutional, 1940-1942, (2 folders) (Box 72)
    - Hemorrhoids and colon health, 1944-1947, (4 folders) (Box 72)
    - Pyorrhea, 1952 (Box 72)
    - Rheumatism and arthritis, 1930-1953, (13 folders) (Box 72)
    - Stimulants (No Doz, etc.), 1943-1953, (11 folders) (Box 72)
    - Stomach relievers
      - Bell Ans, 1939-1953, (13 folders) (Box 72)
      - Bell Ans, 1930-1938, (4 folders) (Box 73)
      - Bi-So-Dol, 1933-1953, (12 folders) (Box 73)
      - Brisochi, 1928-1953, (10 folders) (Box 73)
      - Choos, 1947-1953, (8 folders) (Box 73)
      - Intesta-Femin, 1915 (Box 73)
      - Jests, 1940-1953, (14 folders) (Box 73)
      - Mother Sill's Seasick Remedy, 1929-1953, (12 folders) (Box 73)
      - Pepto-Bismol, 1942-1953, (10 folders) (Box 73)
      - Phillips Milk of Magnesia, 1949-1953, (4 folders) (Box 73)
      - Phillips Milk of Magnesia, 1944-1950, (6 folders) (Box 74)
      - Tums, 1947-1953, (6 folders) (Box 74)
      - Udga Tablets, 1942-1953, (12 folders) (Box 74)
      - Von's Tablets, 1942-1953, (12 folders) (Box 74)
      - Pape's, 1928-1937 (Box 74)
      - Dr. Tripp's Liquor Rheumatica, 1927 (Box 74)
      - Nurito, 1934-1941, (2 folders) (Box 74)
      - Acidine, 1929-1932 (Box 74)
      - Calcium Wafers, 1930 (Box 74)
      - Gastrogen, 1928-1930 (Box 74)
  - Food Products
    - Baby Food
      - Gerber's, 1949-1951, (3 folders) (Box 74)
      - Gerber's, 1930-1948, (8 folders) (Box 75)
      - Heinz, 1935-1953, (17 folders) (Box 75)
      - Lacricin, 1929 (Box 75)
      - Libby's, 1935-1940 (Box 75)
      - Mellin's, 1932-1934 (Box 75)
      - Nestle, 1923-1927, (2 folders) (Box 75)
      - Nestle, 1928-1934, (2 folders) (Box 76)
      - Robinson's Patent Barley, 1932 (Box 76)
      - Similac, 1933-1934 (Box 76)
      - S.M.A., 1931-1934, (2 folders) (Box 76)
      - Hygeia, 1931-1932 (Box 76)
      - Lactogen, 1927 (Box 76)
      - Mellin's, 1927-1931, (2 folders) (Box 76)
      - Mead's Dextro-Maltose, 1930-1932 (Box 76)
      - Miscellaneous, 1942-1954, (13 folders) (Box 76)
      - Pablum, 1954 (Box 76)
    - Baking Powder
      - Calumet, 1930-1942, (9 folders) (Box 76)
      - Calumet, 1923-1927, (5 folders) (Box 77)
      - Canadian Royal, 1924 (Box 77)
      - Clabber Girl, 1934-1942, (2 folders) (Box 77)
      - Davis, 1923-1944, (3 folders) (Box 77)
      - Eggo, 1934 (Box 77)
      - K.C., 1930-1934 (Box 77)
      - Magic, 1927-1942, (4 folders) (Box 77)
  - Leather Goods, 1947-1949, (3 folders) (Box 77)
  - Welfare and Religious Organizations (Red Cross and others), 1954 (Box 77)
  - Food Products
    - Bread
      - Mother Hubbard, 1930 (Box 78)
      - Oh Boy, 1934-1936 (Box 78)
      - Peak Frean, 1929-1937, (2 folders) (Box 78)
      - Rice's, 1941 (Box 78)
      - Ry-Krisp, 1930-1941, (12 folders) (Box 78)
      - Mrs. Schmidt's, 1927-1929, (2 folders) (Box 78)
      - Schrafft's, 1941-1942, (2 folders) (Box 78)
      - Schulze's, 1929 (Box 78)
      - Silvercup, 1941-1953, (12 folders) (Box 78)
      - Southern Bread, 1928 (Box 78)
      - Stone Baking Co., 1939 (Box 78)
      - Taggart's, 1928 (Box 78)
      - Taystee, 1930-1953, (11 folders) (Box 78)
      - Thomas, 1930-1952, (11 folders) (Box 78)
      - Thomas, 1944-1950, (8 folders) (Box 79)
      - Town Talk, 1942 (Box 79)
      - Arnold, 1948-1949, (2 folders) (Box 79)
      - Bond, 1949 (Box 79)
      - Van de Kamp's, 1930-1933, (2 folders) (Box 79)
      - Ward (Tip Top), 1922-1944, (13 folders) (Box 79)
      - Weber's, 1931-1933, (3 folders) (Box 79)
      - Wheat King, 1928-1929 (Box 79)
      - White Rose, 1927-1928, (2 folders) (Box 79)
      - Wonder, 1929-1954, (19 folders) (Box 80)
      - Wonder, 1927-1932 (Box 81)
      - Miscellaneous, 1943-1953, (11 folders) (Box 81)
      - Miscellaneous, 1927-1942, (10 folders) (Box 82)
    - Bouillon Cubes and Meat Extracts, 1951 (Box 82)
    - Butter and Butter Substitutes
      - Abbott's, 1932 (Box 82)
      - Borden's, 1932 (Box 82)
      - Cudahy's Delrich Margarine, 1947-1953, (7 folders) (Box 82)
      - Cedar Brook, 1928-1929 (Box 82)
      - Durkee's Margarine, 1947-1953, (7 folders) (Box 82)
      - Durkee's Margarine, 1943-1946, (4 folders) (Box 83)
      - Jelke's Goodluck, 1929-1954, (11 folders) (Box 83)
      - Land O' Lakes, 1929-1954, (9 folders) (Box 83)
      - Meadow Gold, 1931-1937, (2 folders) (Box 83)
      - Morning Glory, 1928-1929 (Box 83)
      - Nucoa Margarine, 1942-1954, (13 folders) (Box 83)
      - Nucoa Margarine, 1924-1941, (9 folders) (Box 84)
      - Parkay Margarine, 1948-1954, (7 folders) (Box 84)
      - Blue Valley, 1927-1932, (2 folders) (Box 84)
      - Jelke's Goodluck, 1920-1928, (2 folders) (Box 84)
      - Gem Nut, 1931 (Box 84)
    - Candy
      - Miscellaneous, 1917-1943, (7 folders) (Box 84)
      - Miscellaneous, 1945-1948, (5 folders) (Box 85)
      - Mars, 1942 (Box 85)
    - Canned Food
      - Borden's, 1943-1952, (9 folders) (Box 85)
      - Ann Page, 1939-1940, (2 folders) (Box 85)
      - Del Monte, 1936-1953, (15 folders) (Box 85)
      - Derby, 1941 (Box 85)
      - Heinz, 1947-1953, (7 folders) (Box 85)
      - Miscellaneous, 1947 (Box 85)
      - Heinz, 1939-1946, (7 folders) (Box 86)
      - Royal Scarlet, 1942-1951, (10 folders) (Box 86)
      - Van Camps, 1941 (Box 86)
      - White Rose, 1943-1947, (5 folders) (Box 86)
      - Canapes (recipes), 1953-1956 (Box 86)
      - Miscellaneous, 1944-1954, (10 folders) (Box 86)
      - Vegetables, 1943-1950, (3 folders) (Box 86)
      - Miscellaneous, 1941-1942, (2 folders) (Box 86)
    - Cereal
      - Armour's Oats, 1915-1925 (Box 86)
      - Carnation Wheat, 1930-1932 (Box 86)
      - Cheerioats, 1949-1952, (4 folders) (Box 86)
      - Cheerioats, 1941-1948, (8 folders) (Box 87)
      - Ralston, 1952 (Box 87)
      - Cream of Wheat, 1940-1953, (13 folders) (Box 87)
      - Force, 1932-1934 (Box 87)
      - Grape Nuts Flakes, 1945-1953, (7 folders) (Box 87)
    - Canned Food
      - Aylmer, 1935 (Box 87)
      - Miscellaneous,, 1948-1953, (4 folders) (Box 87)
      - Miscellaneous, 1943-1947, (5 folders) (Box 88)
      - Bean Hole, 1927 (Box 88)
      - Brown Beauty, 1919-1922 (Box 88)
      - California Asparagus, 1926-1930 (Box 88)
      - California Limas, 1928-1935 (Box 88)
      - Campbell's Beans, 1922-1935, (3 folders) (Box 88)
      - Miscellaneous, 1946-1953, (13 folders) (Box 88)
      - Miscellaneous, 1949 (Box 89)
      - Corn, 1943-1951, (9 folders) (Box 89)
      - Clark's, 1932 (Box 89)
      - Peas, 1943-1954, (12 folders) (Box 89)
      - Miscellaneous, 1938-1954, (8 folders) (Box 89)
      - Miscellaneous, 1927-1946, (7 folders) (Box 90)
    - Vegetables Fresh and Dried, 1930-1954, (14 folders) (Box 90)
    - Rice, 1921-1954, (13 folders) (Box 90)
    - Meat Spreads, 1946 (Box 90)
    - Rice
      - Uncle Ben's Converted Rice, 1947-1952, (6 folders) (Box 91)
      - Comet, 1928-1941 (Box 91)
      - River, 1935-1942, (2 folders) (Box 91)
      - Southern Rice Industry, 1936 (Box 91)
      - Whitehouse, 1934 (Box 91)
      - Miscellaneous, 1952-1953, (2 folders) (Box 91)
    - Sandwich Spreads, 1939 (Box 91)
    - Chewing Gum
      - Miscellaneous, 1943 (Box 91)
      - Adams, 1919-1940, (3 folders) (Box 91)
      - Beech-Nut, 1931-1947, (5 folders) (Box 91)
      - Beeman's, 1931-1934 (Box 91)
      - Dentyne, 1917-1942, (3 folders) (Box 91)
      - Dentyne, 1935-1940 (Box 92)
      - Fleers, 1939 (Box 92)
      - Teaberry, 1928-1929 (Box 92)
      - Tempters, 1934-1935 (Box 92)
      - Miscellaneous, 1947-1953, (2 folders) (Box 92)
      - Wrigley's, 1921-1954, (14 folders) (Box 92)
      - Wrigley's, 1945-1947, (3 folders) (Box 93)
      - Miscellaneous, 1944-1954, (9 folders) (Box 93)
  - Household Goods
    - Towels, 1950-1952, (3 folders) (Box 93)
    - Fabrics and Textile Processes--Sanforized, 1947-1954, (7 folders) (Box 93)
    - Cameras and Equipment
      - Ansco, 1949-1954, (2 folders) (Box 93)
      - Argus, 1949-1954, (2 folders) (Box 93)
      - Miscellaneous, 1949-1954, (4 folders) (Box 93)
  - Beverages
    - Coffee
      - Aborn's, 1944-1953, (8 folders) (Box 94)
      - Admiration, 1945-1947, (3 folders) (Box 94)
      - Airway, 1936-1953, (12 folders) (Box 94)
      - A&P, 1932-1953, (16 folders) (Box 94)
      - Astor, 1928-1934 (Box 94)
      - A&P, 1931, 1950, 1953, (3 folders) (Box 95)
      - Astor, 1900s-1928 (Box 95)
      - Atwood, 1934-1942, (2 folders) (Box 95)
      - Harrington Hall, 1909-1950, (7 folders) (Box 95)
      - Beech-Nut, 1917-1953, (19 folders) (Box 95)
      - Beech-Nut, 1929-1940, (2 folders) (Box 96)
      - Bevo, 1917-1920, n.d., (2 folders) (Box 96)
      - Blue Plate, (4 folders) (Box 96)
      - Borden's, 1920-1953, (10 folders) (Box 96)
      - Boscul, 1945-1949, (3 folders) (Box 96)
      - Breakstone, 1945 (Box 96)
      - Butter Nut, 1922-1939, (4 folders) (Box 96)
      - Café du Monde, 1928 (Box 96)
      - Café Rico, 1939-1940, (2 folders) (Box 96)
      - Camp, 1914-1928 (Box 96)
      - Canova, 1930-1934, (2 folders) (Box 96)
      - Caswell's, 1928-1932 (Box 96)
      - Chase & Sanborn, 1949-1953, (4 folders) (Box 96)
      - C.W. Brand, 1930 (Box 96)
      - Del Monte, 1930-1948, (8 folders) (Box 96)
      - Don De, 1949-1950, (2 folders) (Box 97)
      - Nestle, 1924 (Box 97)
      - A&P, 1940 (Box 97)
      - Beech-Nut, 1947 (Box 97)
      - Chase & Sanborn, 1954 (Box 97)
      - Del Monte, 1932 (Box 97)
  - Food Products
    - Crackers and Biscuits
      - Miscellaneous, 1917-1954, (12 folders) (Box 97)
      - Trix, 1939 (Box 97)
      - Vegetized Wafers, 1929-1930 (Box 97)
      - Miscellaneous, 1946-1949, (4 folders) (Box 98)
    - Cooking Oil
      - Mazola, 1928-1954, (11 folders) (Box 98)
      - Planter's HI-Hat, 1934-1936 (Box 98)
      - Spry, 1936-1938 (Box 98)
      - Wesson, 1945-1954, (9 folders) (Box 98)
      - Miscellaneous, 1943-1954, (10 folders) (Box 98)
      - Miscellaneous, 1952 (Box 99)
      - Wesson, 1947 (Box 99)
    - Fish
      - Beardsley's, 1928-1931, (2 folders) (Box 99)
      - Birdseye, 1932 (Box 99)
      - Burnham & Morrill Co., 1929-1931 (Box 99)
      - Canned Salmon, 1936-1941, (3 folders) (Box 99)
      - Chatka, 1931-1938, (5 folders) (Box 99)
      - Chicken of the Sea, 1929-1941, (7 folders) (Box 99)
      - Davis, 1928-1929, (2 folders) (Box 99)
      - Del Monte, 1933-1940, (4 folders) (Box 99)
      - 40 Fathom Fish, 1928-1941, (2 folders) (Box 99)
      - Geisha, 1941 (Box 99)
      - Gorton's, 1928-1954, (24 folders) (Box 99)
      - Icy Point, 1930 (Box 99)
      - Japanese Deep Sea Crabmeat, 1930-1937, (5 folders) (Box 99)
      - Long Island Oysters, 1932 (Box 99)
      - Namco, 1935-1937 (Box 99)
      - Nordic, 1929 (Box 99)
      - Pioneer, 1929 (Box 100)
      - Van Camps, 1935 (Box 100)
      - Canned Miscellaneous, 1954 (Box 100)
      - Frozen Miscellaneous, 1954 (Box 100)
      - Miscellaneous, 1939-1953, (8 folders) (Box 100)
      - Canned Shrimp, 1941 (Box 100)
    - Crackers
      - Beech-Nut, 1927-1940, (2 folders) (Box 100)
      - Colonial, 1930 (Box 100)
      - Creamettes, 1933 (Box 100)
      - Edgemont, 1925-1933 (Box 100)
      - Educator, 1912-1933 (Box 100)
      - Huntley & Palmers, 1925-1942, (2 folders) (Box 100)
      - Ivins, 1932 (Box 100)
      - Johnston, 1934 (Box 100)